{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868671428","data":{"timestamp":" 946868671428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868690054","data":{"timestamp":" 946868690054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868695586","data":{"timestamp":" 946868695586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868701826","data":{"timestamp":" 946868701826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868707760","data":{"timestamp":" 946868707760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868718265","data":{"timestamp":" 946868718265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868722856","data":{"timestamp":" 946868722856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868728186","data":{"timestamp":" 946868728186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868742265","data":{"timestamp":" 946868742265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868747928","data":{"timestamp":" 946868747928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868753715","data":{"timestamp":" 946868753714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868769143","data":{"timestamp":" 946868769142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" bb5138b2-73bc-4f8d-bcdc-944ea5791537"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868810687","data":{"timestamp":" 946868810687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868815958","data":{"timestamp":" 946868815958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868822770","data":{"timestamp":" 946868822770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868828928","data":{"timestamp":" 946868828927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868857699","data":{"timestamp":" 946868857699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868863601","data":{"timestamp":" 946868863601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868867962","data":{"timestamp":" 946868867962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868873293","data":{"timestamp":" 946868873293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868878379","data":{"timestamp":" 946868878379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868887902","data":{"timestamp":" 946868887901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868893676","data":{"timestamp":" 946868893674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" e85c531d-6f62-4d55-a372-acc752a28091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868916541","data":{"timestamp":" 946868916541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868916924","data":{"timestamp":" 946868916924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868917157","data":{"timestamp":" 946868917157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868917471","data":{"timestamp":" 946868917471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868917705","data":{"timestamp":" 946868917705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868921159","data":{"timestamp":" 946868921158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868921463","data":{"timestamp":" 946868921462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868922386","data":{"timestamp":" 946868922386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868922819","data":{"timestamp":" 946868922819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868925750","data":{"timestamp":" 946868925749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868926040","data":{"timestamp":" 946868926039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868926898","data":{"timestamp":" 946868926897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868927577","data":{"timestamp":" 946868927576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868928327","data":{"timestamp":" 946868928327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868928665","data":{"timestamp":" 946868928665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868928954","data":{"timestamp":" 946868928953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868929267","data":{"timestamp":" 946868929267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868929531","data":{"timestamp":" 946868929531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868933242","data":{"timestamp":" 946868933241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868933637","data":{"timestamp":" 946868933636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868933882","data":{"timestamp":" 946868933881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868934205","data":{"timestamp":" 946868934205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868934449","data":{"timestamp":" 946868934448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868937925","data":{"timestamp":" 946868937924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868938232","data":{"timestamp":" 946868938231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868939163","data":{"timestamp":" 946868939162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868939597","data":{"timestamp":" 946868939597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868942529","data":{"timestamp":" 946868942528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868942822","data":{"timestamp":" 946868942821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868943678","data":{"timestamp":" 946868943677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868944354","data":{"timestamp":" 946868944354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868945104","data":{"timestamp":" 946868945103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868945441","data":{"timestamp":" 946868945440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868945728","data":{"timestamp":" 946868945727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868946061","data":{"timestamp":" 946868946061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868946344","data":{"timestamp":" 946868946343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868949790","data":{"timestamp":" 946868949788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868949873","data":{"timestamp":" 946868949873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 30bd38d2-2f30-4e76-baea-84603f8c0889"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868970128","data":{"timestamp":" 946868970128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868970511","data":{"timestamp":" 946868970511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868970744","data":{"timestamp":" 946868970744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868971057","data":{"timestamp":" 946868971057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868971290","data":{"timestamp":" 946868971290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868974691","data":{"timestamp":" 946868974690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868974984","data":{"timestamp":" 946868974983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868975887","data":{"timestamp":" 946868975886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868976309","data":{"timestamp":" 946868976309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868979192","data":{"timestamp":" 946868979192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868979476","data":{"timestamp":" 946868979475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868980319","data":{"timestamp":" 946868980318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868980981","data":{"timestamp":" 946868980981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868981715","data":{"timestamp":" 946868981715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868982039","data":{"timestamp":" 946868982039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868982313","data":{"timestamp":" 946868982313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868982626","data":{"timestamp":" 946868982626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868982890","data":{"timestamp":" 946868982890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868986567","data":{"timestamp":" 946868986567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868986950","data":{"timestamp":" 946868986949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868987183","data":{"timestamp":" 946868987182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868987496","data":{"timestamp":" 946868987495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868987728","data":{"timestamp":" 946868987728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868991149","data":{"timestamp":" 946868991149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868991442","data":{"timestamp":" 946868991442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868992344","data":{"timestamp":" 946868992344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868992768","data":{"timestamp":" 946868992767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868995635","data":{"timestamp":" 946868995635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868995917","data":{"timestamp":" 946868995917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868996761","data":{"timestamp":" 946868996761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868997425","data":{"timestamp":" 946868997425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868998158","data":{"timestamp":" 946868998158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868998483","data":{"timestamp":" 946868998483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868998757","data":{"timestamp":" 946868998757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868999071","data":{"timestamp":" 946868999070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868999334","data":{"timestamp":" 946868999334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869002803","data":{"timestamp":" 946869002802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869002923","data":{"timestamp":" 946869002923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" c2804a3c-3d38-4931-8859-3d514072bfb4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869037214","data":{"timestamp":" 946869037214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_wu-mba-ha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869046061","data":{"timestamp":" 946869046061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_nchi-ha-nyi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869056551","data":{"timestamp":" 946869056551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_la-ha-bu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869072108","data":{"timestamp":" 946869072108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ke-msta-ha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" msta"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869093932","data":{"timestamp":" 946869093932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ke-msta-ha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" msta"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869107343","data":{"timestamp":" 946869107342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ke-msta-ha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869119136","data":{"timestamp":" 946869119136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-nde-twe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869126792","data":{"timestamp":" 946869126792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-nde-twe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869215071","data":{"timestamp":" 946869215071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-mmo-nye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869221817","data":{"timestamp":" 946869221816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-kwi-ta"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869227881","data":{"timestamp":" 946869227881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-ndi-wi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869234797","data":{"timestamp":" 946869234797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-hi-bu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869241194","data":{"timestamp":" 946869241194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_pi-ha-ze"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869246951","data":{"timestamp":" 946869246950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 1af96acc-6830-4ce9-a1cd-f6fc3705c1da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_pi-ha-ze"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869273689","data":{"timestamp":" 946869273689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-hi-bu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869280363","data":{"timestamp":" 946869280363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_la-ha-bu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869289202","data":{"timestamp":" 946869289202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-kwi-ta"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869306300","data":{"timestamp":" 946869306300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ke-msta-ha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869313280","data":{"timestamp":" 946869313280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_wu-mba-ha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869320816","data":{"timestamp":" 946869320816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-ndi-wi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869326826","data":{"timestamp":" 946869326825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-nde-twe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869333278","data":{"timestamp":" 946869333278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_pi-ha-ze"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869338775","data":{"timestamp":" 946869338775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_ha-mmo-nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870179526","data":{"timestamp":" 946870179526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_nchi-ha-nyi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870185311","data":{"timestamp":" 946870185309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_060406"," gameId":" 35f61955-125e-457c-a0f0-6c6be40ca9fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ha..ha.syl.rand.all.stat.show.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ha_nchi-ha-nyi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}